shopjustice.com 2019-10-08

# Justice Privacy Policy | Justice

## PRIVACY POLICY

**Updated and Effective:** February 23, 2019

This Privacy Policy applies to any website, application, feature, widget or other online service that is owned or controlled by Justice (part of Tween Brands, Inc., which is a subsidiary of Ascena Retail Group, Inc.) (" **Justice** "), that posts a link to this Privacy Policy (collectively, the “ **Channels** ”) and by Justice offline. This policy does not apply to the Live Justice mobile app, which is governed by a separate privacy policy available [here.](https://app.shopjustice.com/parents/legal/privacy)

**By accessing, using, or otherwise interacting with any part of our Channels, or by otherwise providing Personal Information to Justice, you agree to be bound by the terms of this Policy and the applicable Terms of Use which govern your use of any Channel. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THE TERMS OF THIS POLICY AND THE APPLICABLE TERMS OF USE, DO NOT ACCESS OR USE THE CHANNELS OR PROVIDE PERSONAL INFORMATION TO US THROUGH ANY CHANNEL.**

#### **This Privacy Policy explains:**

  * Key Points
  * Information We Collect
  * Children
  * Our Use of Information
  * Sharing of Information
  * Third-Party Links & Content
  * Online Advertising and Analytics
  * How We Respond To "Do Not Track" Signals
  * Security
  * Consent To Transfer and Storage In The United States
  * Accessing and Updating Information and Choices
  * Your California Privacy Rights
  * Changes To This Privacy Policy
  * Contact Us

#### Key Points

Please review our full Privacy Policy below before using our Channels, but here is a summary of some important information: 

How Does Justice Use the Information it Collects?

When we collect or receive information about our users and customers, we primarily use this information in connection with your relationship with Justice, including making it possible for you to use the features of our Channels and to provide you with special offers and content we think will most interest you. 

How Do Companies within the Ascena Retail Family of Brands Share Information?

When you shop with us or interact with us through one of our Channels, we share information with our sister companies in the [Ascena Retail family of brands](https://www.ascenaretail.com/). We will use this information to better understand our customers and improve your shopping and browsing experience. Other brands may also contact you with marketing information, such as special offers and promotions. If you would prefer that we not make your Personal Information available to our sister companies for their own direct marketing purposes, you can use the opt-out available in our Preference Center. California residents, see “Your California Privacy Rights.” 

Does Justice Share Information with Other Third Parties?

While we share non-Personal Information we collect (such as information about how visitors interact with our Channels and hashed or de-identified information) with third parties in our discretion, we share Personal Information only as described in our full Privacy Policy, below. We share Personal Information when you consent, with third parties so that they can market products and services to you, with service providers that help us operate the Channels, with the issuing bank that provides our co-branded credit cards, in the event of a corporate restructuring, and as required by law. You can tell us not to share your Personal Information with unaffiliated third parties for their own direct marketing purposes by visiting our Preference Center. California residents, see “Your California Privacy Rights.” 

How Does Justice Work with Third-Party Analytics and Advertising Companies?

We work with online advertising and analytics providers to serve our ads online and provide us with information regarding traffic on the Channels. The companies with which we work may use information about your activities on the Channels – and other websites and services you visit across the various devices you use – to recognize you and your devices across the internet and to provide you targeted advertising based upon your interests. Some of these companies participate in self-regulatory programs that allow you to opt-out of having information about you used for targeted advertising purposes, and you may access those opt-outs at [optout.networkadvertising.org](https://optout.networkadvertising.org/) and [optout.aboutads.info](https://optout.aboutads.info/) We also set our own cookie in coordination with our online advertising vendor Conversant, LLC to assist us in determining which of our offers and advertisements to serve you. To opt-out of this cookie, click [here](http://dtmc.shopjustice.com/adinfo/choice/prod/?type=fpc&cid=3270&cname=Justice&cmagic=3f7bcd&clogo=3270.png&loc=us&lang=en-us). Please note these mechanisms will not stop you from seeing ads while you are online. If you opt-out, you will see generic ads instead of ads targeted to your interests. 

What if I am a Resident of California?

If you are a resident of California, please see “Your California Privacy Rights.” 

#### Information We Collect

Through various features on the Channels, we may collect personal information, which is information that is linked to a specific, identifiable individual ("Personal Information"), such as first and last name, email addresses, postal addresses, and telephone numbers. We may also collect other information about you, such as payment card data or other payment information, information about your purchases and other transactions with us, demographic information (e.g., your gender, ZIP code/postal code, or similar information), information about the device you are using to access the Channels, and information about your preferences and interests. We may also offer features through which you may choose to provide us with information that may be considered to include biometric identifiers (e.g., imaging used to help fit clothing). We may take your Personal Information and make it non-personally identifiable, either by combining it with information about other individuals and/or by hashing the information or otherwise removing characteristics that make the information personally identifiable directly to you. 

If we combine demographic, preference or similar information with the Personal Information we collect, we will treat the combined information as Personal Information under this Privacy Policy. The information we collect may be provided by you or by a third party, or may be collected automatically. We may combine the information we collect online with information we collect in our stores or elsewhere offline. 

Information You Provide. We may ask you to provide certain information to us (including your Personal Information) when you use the Channels or offline. For example, you may give us your information when making a purchase or completing another transaction, joining our affiliate program, interacting with customer service (including live chat), and through interactive features. When interacting with customer service, you may have the option to allow our representatives to share your screen. If you choose to permit screen sharing, we may be able to view any data and applications present on your device screen at that time. You may choose not to provide certain information; however, choosing to do so may prevent you from being able to take advantage of some of our offered features or from conducting transactions. 

Community Forums and User Submission. The Channels may provide you the opportunity to submit information to us, through interactive features, and through other communication functionality ("Community Forums"). You may choose, through such features or otherwise, to submit or post “User Submissions” (which means any and all information and content that you submit or post to the Channels, including, without limitation, photos, audio, video, messages, text, files, or other content you provide us and as further described in our Terms of Use). Some features, such as user reviews, may be operated by a third party and your postings also may be subject to the third party’s privacy policy and terms of use. 

Please note that certain information, such as your name and/or place of residence, may be publicly displayed on the Channels along with your User Submissions. Your use of any Community Forum is subject to our Terms of Use, including without limitation the “User Comments & Postings” section. Note that anything you submit through a public-facing Community Forum may be made public – others will have access to your User Submission and may use it or share it with third parties. We are not responsible for the actions of third parties and the use of your information and other User Submissions by such third parties is not subject to the protections of this Privacy Policy. 

Functionality on the Channels may permit interactions that you initiate between the Channels and a third-party service such as Facebook (“Social Networking Features”). Examples of Social Networking Features include enabling you to “like” or “share” content from the Channels or to “like” or “share” our page on a third-party service; to automatically or selectively show your social media posts on the Channels; and to otherwise connect the Channels to a third-party service. If you choose to share content or to otherwise post information through the Channels to a third-party service, or vice versa, that information may be publicly displayed. Similarly, if you post information on a third-party service that references us (for example, by using a hashtag associated with us in your post), your post may be published on the Channels or otherwise in accordance with the terms of that third party. Also, both we and the third party may have access to certain information about you and your use of the Channels and the third-party service. In addition, we may receive information about you if other users of a third-party service give us access to their profiles and you are one of their “connections” or information about you is otherwise accessible through your profile or similar page on a social networking or other third-party service. The information we collect in connection with Social Networking Features is subject to this Privacy Policy. The information collected and stored by the third party remains subject to the third party’s privacy practices, including whether the third party continues to share information with us, the types of information shared, and your choices with regard to what is visible to others on that third-party service. 

If you submit User Submissions or use Social Networking Features, we may publish that information or content online or offline, including in connection with our advertising, marketing, publicity, and promotional activities, as further described in our Terms of Use

We may obtain information, including Personal Information and demographic information, about you from third parties, including our joint marketing partners, third-party websites, affiliate program service providers, the bank that operates our private label credit card program, users who provide us with information about others (i.e. purchasing a gift card for someone else), or other unrelated third parties. We may combine information about you that we have with information we obtain from business partners or other companies. In those cases, we will apply this Privacy Policy to the combined information. Please note that if you apply for or utilize a Justice-branded credit card, you are providing your information to the bank that administers the credit card, which will share that information with us. 

Send-to-a-Friend Features. We may make available on the Channels a “send-to-a-friend,” “refer a friend,” “wishlist” or similar function that permits you to send Channel content directly to a third party through the Channels. If you send a friend a communication using such functionality, the information you provide about your friend (e.g., name and e-mail address) is used to facilitate the communication and is not used for any other marketing purpose unless we obtain consent from that person. 

Justice and our third-party service providers, including analytics providers, advertisers, and third-party content providers, may automatically or passively receive and record certain information about your use of the Channels whenever you visit or interact with the Channels, such as: your IP address, mobile device identifier, or similar device identifier; browser type; type of device you use to access the Channels; the domain name from which you arrived at the Channels; the time of day you visit our Channels; Location Data (defined below); and specific pages or areas of the Channel through which you navigate and how you interact with those pages or areas ("Usage Information"). This information helps us create a better experience for our users and provide you with targeted advertising. Please see the “Online Advertising and Analytics Providers” section below for more information about how to control the use of your Personal Information for the purposes of advertising. 

We may capture and record or infer certain location data regarding your use of the Channels and your travels ("Location Data"). We may link that Location Data to other information that you provide to us or that may be accessed in connection with your use of the Channels. We may directly collect precise Location Data from the device you use to access the Channels if you have opted-in to such collection through our mobile application or your browser. You may be able to turn off the collection of precise Location Data through your device settings. However, please note that we may still be able to infer your approximate location through other information we collect, such as IP address. 

The methods used to collect Usage Information may include: 

Cookies and Local Storage. “Cookies” and local storage are pieces of information (data files) transferred to an individual’s browser on their device when the device is used to visit a Channel. These technologies are able to store a unique identifier for a device to allow a certain Internet site to recognize the device whenever the device is used to visit the site. These technologies may be used for many purposes by us and our third-party service providers, such as automatically collecting Usage Information, enabling features, remembering your preferences, and providing you with targeted advertising elsewhere online. If you do not want to accept cookies, you can block them by adjusting the settings on your Internet browser. You can find more information about cookies and how they work at [www.allaboutcookies.org](https://www.allaboutcookies.org/). 

Certain browsers or browser add-ons, such as Adobe Flash, may provide additional local data storage mechanisms that are used in a manner similar to cookies, and some of the content included on our Channels may make use of this local storage. For example, a Flash cookie is a data file placed on a device via the Adobe Flash plug-in that may be built into or downloaded by you onto your device. Flash cookies may be used for various purposes, including, without limitation, enabling a Flash feature and remembering your preferences. For more information about Flash and the privacy choices Adobe offers, visit [http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager.html](https://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager.html). If you choose to disable cookies, to adjust your Flash privacy settings on your device, or to otherwise restrict local storage, some features of the Channels may not function properly, including the shopping cart and ordering processes. 

Web Beacons. Small graphic images or other web programming code called web beacons (also known as “pixel tags,” “1x1 GIFs,” or “clear GIFs”) may be included in our web pages and email messages. Web beacons may be invisible to you, but any electronic image or other web programming code inserted into a web page or email can act as a web beacon. Web beacons or similar technologies may be used for a number of purposes, including, without limitation, to count visitors to a Channel, to monitor how users navigate the Channel, to count how many emails that were sent were actually opened or to count how many particular links were actually viewed. 

Embedded Scripts. An embedded script is programming code that is designed to collect information about your interactions with the Channels, such as the links you click on. The code is temporarily downloaded onto your device from our server or a third-party service provider, is active only while you are connected to a Channel, and is deactivated or deleted thereafter. 

In addition, we may use a variety of other technologies that collect similar information for security and fraud detection purposes. 

#### Children

Our Channels that post this privacy policy are primarily e-commerce in nature and are intended for a general audience. We do not knowingly collect personal information online from children younger than the age of 13 unless doing so is in compliance with applicable law, including, for residents of the United States, the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act. Please note that this policy does not apply to the Live Justice mobile app, which is governed by a separate children’s privacy policy available [here](https://app.shopjustice.com/parents/legal/privacy). 

#### Our Use of Information

We may use information collected from or about you, including your Personal Information and Usage Information, to:  

  * allow you participate in the Channels, or features or activities we offer, including sweepstakes, contests, or other prize promotions;
  * process a transaction (through our Channels or in our stores) or your account registration, verify your identity or eligibility, and send you confirmations and receipts;
  * send you information and special offers from us, our advertisers, or third-party business partners; to contact you regarding any problems with your merchandise order or account; and to respond to your inquiries and provide customer service related to your use of the Channels;
  * administer and manage our affiliate program, through which third parties make money by referring customers to our Channels;
  * protect each party from errors, misuse of the Channels, fraud, or any criminal activity;
  * help us serve you better, including personalizing your shopping experience and tailoring content, recommendations, and offers we display to you, including advertisements, both on the Channels and elsewhere online;
  * improve the Channels or our products and services and for legal, regulatory and internal business purposes;
  * detect and troubleshoot problems, resolve disputes, and enforce applicable agreements and policies for the Channels; and
  * fulfill any other purpose consistent with this Privacy Policy or for purposes disclosed to you at the time of collection or with your consent.

#### Sharing of Information

We may share non-personal information, such as Usage Information, hashed or otherwise de-identified data, and aggregated user statistics, with third parties in our discretion. We may share the information we have collected about you (including Personal Information) in the circumstances described below or elsewhere in this Privacy Policy, as disclosed at the time you provide information or otherwise with your consent. 

Affiliated and Unaffiliated Third Parties for Direct Marketing

Justice may share your information, including Personal Information, with Ascena Retail Group, Inc. (the parent company of Justice), other brands owned by Ascena Retail Group, and its and our affiliates and subsidiaries, for business, analytical, and operational purposes. We also share Personal Information with these affiliated companies so that they may contact you with their own direct marketing. We may share Personal Information with unaffiliated third parties as well (which may include advertising member networks and other data cooperatives) for their own direct marketing purposes and those of such unaffiliated third parties’ own clients. You may opt out of our sharing Personal Information we have collected about you with third parties for their direct marketing purposes as described in the “Updating Your Personal Information and Choices” section below. Please note that if you have separately signed up to receive marketing communications from another Ascena brand, you will need to follow the opt-out procedures offered by that brand in order to stop receiving marketing messages from that brand. Using the affiliate opt-out feature described below will not affect your receipt of marketing messages from other Ascena brands that you have interacted with directly. And, if we have shared your information prior to you exercising your right to opt-out, you will need to opt-out directly with any third party who contacts you with marketing communications. 

Third Parties Providing Services on Our Behalf

We may use third-party service providers to perform certain services on our behalf, such as hosting the Channels or Channel features, delivering packages, processing credit card payments, processing transactions and fulfilling orders, removing repetitive information from customer lists, providing customer service, providing website usage analytics, providing search results and links (including paid listings and links), providing targeted advertising, sending email, direct mail or other communications, providing marketing assistance and data analysis or enhancement, or performing other administrative services. We may give these service providers access to your information (including Personal Information) so that they can carry out the services they are performing for you or for Justice. 

One company with whom we may work is Borderfree, a U.S.-based service provider that we may contract with to facilitate the sale and fulfillment of international online purchases. Where Borderfree will be used to fulfill your international purchase, information that you provide during the checkout process will be collected by or provided to Borderfree and will be processed in accordance with Borderfree’s own privacy policy. By making such a purchase, you agree to [Borderfree’s Privacy Policy](https://www.borderfree.com/privacy/en_us/\)%20and%20Terms%20&%20Conditions%20of%20Use%20\(www.borderfree.com/terms/en_us). 

When You Agree to Receive Information from Third Parties or Request That We Share Your Information.

You may be presented with an opportunity to receive information or marketing offers from one or more third parties. If you agree at that time to have your Personal Information shared, your Personal Information will be disclosed to that third party (or parties) and will be subject to the privacy policy and practices of that third party. We are not responsible for the privacy policies and practices of third parties, and, if you later decide that you no longer want to receive communications from a third party, you will need to contact that third party directly. You also may request, sometimes through your use of an interactive feature or third-party application, that we share information about you with a third party, and we will typically do so under those circumstances. 

Cobranded Credit Card

Justice may share Personal Information and other information with the issuing bank for our Justice Credit Card, and its affiliates, for purposes related to the Justice Credit Card. For example, we may share information in order to send joint offerings, including information on how to apply for the Justice Credit Card, and in connection with your use of a Justice Credit Card, such as to maintain or service accounts and to effectuate transactions. We may also share information with these parties for analytics purposes. 

Other Cobranded Partners

Cobranded partners are entities with whom we work to offer a service or feature. You can typically tell when you are accessing a service offered by a cobranded partner because the cobranded partner’s name will be featured prominently. You may be asked to provide information about yourself to utilize a feature offered by a cobranded partner. In doing so, you may be providing your information to both us and to the cobranded partner, or we may share your information directly with the cobranded partner. Please note that the cobranded partner’s policies will apply its collection and use of your information, not this policy. 

We may also offer scrip programs (which allow you to instruct us to divert a percentage of the amount you spend on purchases to participating schools and other non-profit organizations) or third-party loyalty programs (which allow you to earn “points” on purchases through a Channel and use the points toward certain rewards offered by the loyalty program). If we offer any scrip, loyalty, or similar program in which Justice is a participating vendor and you choose to participate, you authorize Justice or our payment processor to provide information about your purchases to the company administering the program. In such case, the information we will share with that program administrator may include your name, payment information, the date and amount of your purchase, and other information. Please note that once we disclose this information, the scrip or loyalty company may use and share it with others in accordance with its own privacy policy. We do not control the privacy practices of third parties and you should review the privacy policy of any scrip or loyalty partner or other cobranded partner before participating. 

Business Transfers and Transitions

In the event Justice goes through a transition (such as a merger, acquisition, bankruptcy or sale of all or a portion of its assets, including, without limitation, during the course of any due diligence process), your information (including your Personal Information) will likely be among the assets transferred. By providing your Personal Information, you agree that we may transfer such information to the acquiring entity without your further consent. 

Sweepstakes, Contests, & Promotions

We may offer sweepstakes, contests, and other promotions (any, a “Promotion”) that may require registration. By participating in a Promotion, you are agreeing to the provisions, conditions, or official rules that govern that Promotion, which may contain specific requirements of you (including, except where prohibited by law, allowing the sponsor(s) of the Promotion to use your name, voice, likeness or other indicia of persona in advertising or marketing materials). If you choose to enter a Promotion, Personal Information may be disclosed to third parties (including, without limitation, a co-sponsor) or the public in connection with the administration of such Promotion, including, without limitation, in connection with winner selection, prize fulfillment, and as required by law or permitted by the Promotion’s terms or official rules (such as on a winners list). 

Administrative and Legal Reasons

Justice reserves the right to use or disclose any information (including Personal Information) as needed to satisfy any law, regulation or legal request; to protect the integrity of the Channels; to fulfill your requests; to cooperate in any law enforcement investigation, an investigation on a public safety matter, or an investigation into claims of intellectual-property infringement; to protect and defend the legal rights or property of Justice, our parent company, affiliates and shareholders, any Channel or its users, or any other party; or, in an emergency, to protect the health and safety of our users or the general public. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction. 

Employment Applications.

If you apply for a job through the Channels, we or our service provider(s) may ask you to provide self-identifying information (such as veteran status, gender, and ethnicity) in conjunction with laws and regulations enforced by, as applicable, the Equal Employment Opportunity Commission and other federal, state, provincial/territorial, and local regulatory agencies. Providing such self-identifying information is voluntary, but if you do provide such information, we and/or our service provider may submit that information to the appropriate government or regulatory agencies to fulfill reporting requirements and use that information to defend against employment-related complaints. 

#### Third-Party Links & Content

The Channels may link to or incorporate websites, advertising or content hosted and served by third parties over which we have no control and which are governed by the privacy policies and business practices of those third parties, including the bank that operates our private-label credit card program. Justice is not responsible for the privacy practices or business practices of any third party. 

#### Online Advertising and Analytics

We may work with network advertisers, ad agencies, analytics service providers, and other vendors to serve our advertisements on third-party websites, apps, and elsewhere online and to provide us with information regarding use of and traffic on the Channels (including without limitation the pages viewed and the actions users take when visiting the Channels) and the effectiveness of our advertisements. For example, if you click on an advertisement for Justice, our service provider(s) may be able to tell us the advertisement you clicked on and where you were viewing the advertisement. The advertisements you see may be served by one or more third parties, who may use information about your activities on the Channels, and other websites and services you visit across the various devices you use, to provide you targeted advertising based upon your interests. Our service providers may collect certain information about your visits to and activity on the Channels and other websites and services and may use this information to target advertising to you. 

These service providers may set and access their own tracking technologies on your device (including without limitation cookies and web beacons) and may otherwise collect or have access to information about you (such as Usage Information and device identifier). Some of these parties may collect Personal Information over time when you visit the Channels or other online websites and services. Cookies and web beacons, including without limitation those set by third-party network advertisers, may be used to (among other things): target advertisements, prevent you from seeing the same advertisements too many times, and conduct research regarding the usefulness of certain advertisements to you. We may share certain information such as device identifiers, Usage Information, records of transactions you conduct on our Channels or offline, and de-identified information with third-party advertising companies, analytics providers, and other vendors for advertising and analytics purposes. In addition, we and our third-party service providers may use this information to perform matching with third-party cookies in order to provide targeted online marketing. 

We use a variety of service providers to perform advertising and analytics services, and some of these companies may be members of the Network Advertising Initiative (“NAI”) or Digital Advertising Alliance (“DAA”). You may wish to visit [optout.networkadvertising.org](https://optout.networkadvertising.org/), which provides information regarding targeted advertising and the opt-out procedures of NAI members. You may also want to visit [optout.aboutads.info](https://optout.aboutads.info/), which provides information regarding targeted advertising and offers an opt-out for DAA-participating companies. 

We use Google Analytics, which uses cookies and similar technologies to collect and analyze information about use of the Channels and report on activities and trends. This service may also collect information regarding the use of other websites, apps, and online resources. You can learn about Google’s practices by going to [google.com/policies/privacy/partners](https://google.com/policies/privacy/partners), and opt out of them by downloading the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on, available at [tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout). 

For mobile apps, you may be able to limit certain advertising practices using the settings on your phone, tablet or other mobile device. You may also download the AppChoices app at [youradchoices.com/appchoices](https://youradchoices.com/appchoices) to opt out of the delivery of interest-based advertisements in participating mobile apps. 

In addition, we set our own cookie in coordination with our online advertising vendor Conversant, LLC (and its service providers) to assist us in determining which of our offers and advertisements to serve you on our Channels or elsewhere online. To opt-out of this cookie, click [here](https://dtmc.shopjustice.com/adinfo/choice/prod/?type=fpc&cid=3270&cname=Justice&cmagic=3f7bcd&clogo=3270.png&loc=us&lang=en-us). Please note that this is a cookie-based opt-out, so it is specific to the browser through which you opt out. If you clear/delete the cookies on your device and/or browser or use a different device or browser, you will need to opt back out using the link above. 

Please note opting out through these mechanisms does not opt you out of being served advertising. You will continue to receive non-targeted advertisements while online. 

#### How We Respond To "Do Not Track" Signals

Some Internet browsers may be configured to send “Do Not Track” signals to the online services that you visit. There is no consensus among industry participants as to what “Do Not Track” means in this context. Like many websites and online services, our Channels do not alter their practices when they receive a “Do Not Track” signal from a visitor’s browser. To find out more about “Do Not Track,” please visit [www.allaboutdnt.com](https://www.allaboutdnt.com/). 

#### Security

We employ commercially reasonable security methods and technologies to help secure your Personal Information, including physical, technological, and organizational protections. However, no system can be guaranteed 100% secure. We therefore cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information that you transmit to us, or that we transmit to you, or guarantee that it will be free from unauthorized access by third parties. You use the Channels and provide us with information at your own initiative and risk. 

#### Consent To Transfer and Storage In The United States

Justice is a United States company. Please be aware that information we collect will be transferred to and processed in the United States and other countries. By using the Channels, or providing us with any information, you fully understand and unambiguously consent to this transfer, processing, and storage of your information in the United States and other jurisdictions, for which the privacy laws may not be as comprehensive as those in the country where you reside and/or are a citizen. As a result, this information may be subject to access requests from governments, courts, or law enforcement in the United States and other countries according to laws in those jurisdictions. 

#### Accessing and Updating Information and Choices

The Channels may contain webpages or applications through which you can correct or update some of the Personal Information you have provided (such as an online account) or through which you may be able to unsubscribe or modify the email newsletters or similar communications we send to you. If you have an online account, you are responsible for maintaining and updating, as applicable, your account registration data with current, accurate, and complete information. You may view, update, and/or edit the registration data you have provided to Justice by logging in to your account and following the appropriate instructions. 

A registered user of a Channel has the right to request the removal of certain content that (s)he has publicly posted on the Channel. A user can request that we remove content (s)he has previously posted by contacting us using the information listed in the “Contact Us” section below. When submitting a request, please be sure to include your full name, email address, and information sufficient to permit us to locate the User Submission(s) for which you are requesting removal (e.g., for product reviews, a URL of the product page and the user name under which you posted your review). In some cases, we may remove only your Personal Information, but maintain the rest of your User Submission. Note that any removal of your public postings in accordance with these procedures does not ensure complete or comprehensive removal of the content or information you posted, which may persist in archival records or may have been copied by third parties while publicly accessible. 

Justice will make requested changes in our active databases as soon as reasonably practicable. Note, however, that we may retain information that you have updated or changed for internal or administrative purposes. Public postings that you have made (if any) will generally not be removed as a result of updating or deleting your registered account (unless you also follow the procedure for removing such posts as described above). 

You have a right to request access to your Personal Information and to request a correction to it if you believe it is inaccurate. If you have submitted Personal Information to Justice and would like to have access to it, or if you would like to have it corrected, please contact us using the contact information provided below. In some cases, we may not be able to allow you to access certain Personal Information, for example if it contains Personal Information of other persons, or for legal reasons. We may require you to verify your identity before allowing you to access your Personal Information. 

You can unsubscribe from our marketing emails through the opt-out mechanism included in each marketing email we send to you. You may also click here to opt-out of (a) our commercial email or direct-mail marketing messages, (b) having your Personal Information made available to affiliated companies within the Ascena family of brands for their direct marketing purposes, and/or (c) sharing of your Personal Information with unaffiliated third parties for their direct marketing purposes. If you sign up to receive SMS or MMS messages that may be offered on the Channels, you may unsubscribe by replying "STOP." 

Note that we reserve the right to send you certain email or postal communications relating to your use of our Channels, service announcements, notices of changes to this Privacy Policy or our other terms, or similar administrative or transactional messages, and these transactional account messages may be unaffected if you choose to opt-out from marketing communications. 

#### Your California Privacy Rights

As stated above in this Privacy Policy, Justice does not share personal information with third parties for their direct marketing purposes (as defined by California Civil Code Section 1798.83) unless we give you choice (an opt-out) before sharing with those third parties. 

If you are a California resident and you have questions about our practices with respect to sharing information with third parties for their direct marketing purposes and your ability to exercise choice, please send your request by email to [privacy@justiceretail.com](mailto:privacy@justiceretail.com) or write us at Justice Privacy Policy, 8323 Walton Parkway, New Albany, OH 43054. You must put the statement “Your California Privacy Rights” in the subject field of your email or in the address line of your envelope. You must include your name, street address, city, state, and ZIP code. We are not responsible for notices that are not labeled or sent properly, or do not have complete information. 

#### Changes To This Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to change or modify this Privacy Policy in our discretion at any time and will notify you of material changes by posting the changed or modified Privacy Policy on our Channels. We may also provide notice to you in other ways in our discretion, such as through contact information you have provided. Any changes will be effective immediately upon the posting of the revised Privacy Policy unless otherwise specified, and your continued use of the Channels after the effective date of the revised Privacy Policy (or such other act as specified in the revised Privacy Policy) will constitute your consent to those changes. However, we will not, without your consent, use your Personal Information in a manner materially different than what was stated at the time your Personal Information was collected. 

#### Contact Us

By mail: Justice Privacy Policy, 8323 Walton Parkway, New Albany, OH 43054.  
By email: [privacy@justiceretail.com](mailto:privacy@justiceretail.com)   
By phone: [1-866-246-5822](tel:1-866-246-5822)

You may also contact our Chief Counsel – IP & Regulatory at the mailing address above.
